A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges to China, 3
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Environmental Business Association of New York State, 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 54, Folder 884)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Mortgage Bankers Association (Debra Erb), 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 54, Folder 885)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Mortgage Bankers Association (Debra Erb), 1999 April 23 - May 3; Digital: 3.5-inch floppy disk (Box 54, Folder 885)
    Debra L. Erb, The Role of Trade Associations in the Development and Implementation of Industry Standards (disk marked "Erb).
  - Trade Associations Workshop - National Association of Realtors, 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 54, Folder 886)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Papers, 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 54, Folder 887)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Papers, 1999 April 23 - May 3; Digital: 3.5-inch floppy disk (Box 54, Folder 887)
    National Committee Brochure; Dr. Kingdon; Rubenstein; all dated April 1999.
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Papers, 1999 April 23-May 3; Digital: 3.5-inch floppy disk (Box 54, Folder 887)
    Spangler.
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Papers, 1999 April 23-May 3; Digital: 3.5-inch floppy disk (Box 54, Folder 887)
    "Nar" (National Association of Realtors) and "Mort" (Mortgage Bankers Association) files.
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Participants, 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 55, Folder 888)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Predeparture Briefing, 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 55, Folder 889)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Report, Itinerary, and Follow-up, 1999 April 23-May 3 (Box 55, Folder 890)
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Report, Itinerary, and Follow-up, 1999 April 23-May 3; FA772:031; Still Images (Box 146, Folder 890)
    Photos of the delegation's various panels and meetings. 23 images plus some duplicates; negatives.
  - Trade Associations Workshop - Report, Itinerary, and Follow-up, 1999 April 23-May 3; FA772:165; Audiovisual - VHS tape of trip. (Box FA772:165)
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Background Materials, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 891)
    Includes notes on meetings in China. Original folder labeled: Flood Article Background Materials.
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Background Materials, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 892)
    Includes clippings and papers from 1991-1998.
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Beijing Meetings, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 893)
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Budget and Additional Funding, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 894)
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Correspondence with Harbin, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 895)
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Other Foreign Invitees, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 896)
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Papers, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 897)
    In English.
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Participants, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 898)
    Original folder labeled "Working Group."
  - Post-Flood Eco-System Recovery Workshop - Planning, Summary, and Follow-UP, 1999 May 8-18 (Box 55, Folder 899)
  - Security and Foreign Policy Delegation - Background and Planning, 2000 January 16-23 (Box 56, Folder 900)
    Original folders variously labeled Arms and Technology Transfer, Arms Control, Foreign and Defense Policy. Delegation focus also described as Foreign Policy Consequences of Arms and Technology Transfers.
  - Security and Foreign Policy Delegation - Background and Planning, 2000 January 16-23 (Box 56, Folder 901)
  - Security and Foreign Policy Delegation - Beijing, 2000 January 16-23 (Box 56, Folder 902)
  - Security and Foreign Policy Delegation - Brochure and Bios, 2000 January 16-23 (Box 56, Folder 903)
  - Security and Foreign Policy Delegation - Participants, 2000 January 16-23 (Box 56, Folder 904)
  - Security and Foreign Policy Delegation - Reports and Follow-Up, 2000 January 16-23 (Box 56, Folder 905)
    Includes published report United States - China Relations: Comparative Security and Foreign Policy Processes, by Evan S. Medeiros.
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Background, Planning, Budget, and Predeparture Briefing, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 56, Folder 906)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Correspondence with China, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 56, Folder 907)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Hong Kong Program, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 56, Folder 908)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Namelists, Bios, and Brochure, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 56, Folder 909)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Namelists, Bios, and Brochure, 2000 March 31-April 14; FA772:032; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 909)
    Group photo of delegation, with identifications.
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Papers, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 56, Folder 910)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Papers and Questions, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 57, Folder 911)
    Booklet of workshop papers and audience questions in English and Chinese.
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Participants, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 57, Folder 912)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Participants, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 57, Folder 913)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Potential Participants, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 57, Folder 914)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Workshop - Report and Final Itinerary, 2000 March 31-April 14 (Box 57, Folder 915)
  - Wetlands Workshop - Background Material, 2000 June 26-July 4 (Box 57, Folder 916)
    NCUSCR survey and exchange program in conjunction with the International Crane Foundation.
  - Wetlands Workshop - Planning and Preparation, 2000 June 26-July 4 (Box 57, Folder 917)
  - Environmental Education Workshop - Background and Briefing, 2001 May 27-June 6 (Box 57, Folder 918)
    Grassroots Environmentalism and Environmental Education Workshop and Study Tour. Funded by grants from the Department of State's Bureau of Education and Cultural Affairs and United Technologies Corporation. Includes budget and UTC grant application.
  - Environmental Education Workshop - Background Material, 2001 May 27-June 6 (Box 57, Folder 919)
    Original file labeled "Briefing Book."
  - Environmental Education Workshop - Brochure, Itinerary, Report, and Follow-up, 2001 May 27-June 6 (Box 57, Folder 920)
  - Environmental Education Workshop - Correspondence, 2001 May 27-June 6 (Box 57, Folder 921)
    Correspondence with delegates and visa arrangements.
  - Environmental Education Workshop - Papers, 2001 May 27-June 6 (Box 57, Folder 922)
    Papers in English and some Chinese translations.
  - Election Transitions 2001 - Background and Planning, 2001 June 12-23 (Box 58, Folder 923)
    Election 2000: Domestic and Foreign Policy Consequences multicity workshop. File contains background readings and correspondence concerning possible participants.
  - Election Transitions 2001 - Background and Planning, 2001 June 12-23 (Box 58, Folder 924)
  - Election Transitions 2001 - Correspondence and Follow-Up, 2001 June 12-23 (Box 58, Folder 925)
  - Election Transitions 2001 - Itinerary, Namelists, Brochure, and Bios, 2001 June 12-23 (Box 58, Folder 926)
  - Election Transitions 2001 - Taiwan, 2001 June 12-23 (Box 58, Folder 927)
  - New Media Delegation - Background and Planning, 2001 September 1-14 (Box 58, Folder 928)
  - New Media Delegation - Brochure, Bios, Itineraries, 2001 September 1-14 (Box 58, Folder 929)
    Visa and travel information added here.
  - New Media Delegation - Correspondence with Participants, 2001 September 1-14 (Box 58, Folder 930)
    Includes briefing materials.
  - New Media Delegation - Report and Follow-Up, 2001 September 1-14 (Box 58, Folder 931)
    Two unidentified publications in Chinese added to this file, along with a 2000 Survey on Internet Usage and Impact in Five Chinese Cities.
  - International Intervention Delegation - Background and Planning, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 58, Folder 932)
    International Intervention and State Sovereignty, multicity program. File includes copies of papers by participants.
  - International Intervention Delegation - Background Materials, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 58, Folder 933)
    International Intervention and State Sovereignty workshop. Original file labeled "Sovereignty Project."
  - International Intervention Delegation - Brochure and Bios, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 59, Folder 934)
    International Intervention and State Sovereignty workshop.
  - International Intervention Delegation - Correspondence with China, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 59, Folder 935)
    International Intervention and State Sovereignty workshop. Beijing, Shanghai, Nanjing.
  - International Intervention Delegation - Correspondence with Participants, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 59, Folder 936)
    International Intervention and State Sovereignty workshop. Visa and personal forms added here.
  - International Intervention Delegation - Itinerary, Report, and Follow-Up, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 59, Folder 937)
  - International Intervention Delegation - Papers, 2002 January 4-16 (Box 59, Folder 938)
    International Intervention and State Sovereignty workshop. Includes papers in English by U. S. and Chinese participants. Folder marked "American Papers Pre-Trip."
  - Mayors Delegation - Background and Planning, 2002 March 16-27 (Box 59, Folder 939)
    Municipal Government Leaders Delegation.
  - Mayors Delegation - Brochure, Namelists, and Bios, 2002 March 16-27 (Box 59, Folder 940)
    Municipal Government Leaders Delegation. Personal information forms added here.
  - Mayors Delegation - Follow-up, 2002 March 16-27 (Box 59, Folder 941)
  - Mayors Delegation - Follow-up, 2002 March 16-27; FA772:033; Still Images (Box 146, Folder 941)
    Group photo of participants, sent by James Jao; unidentified snapshot of a couple of delegates surrounded by a small group of Chinese.
  - WTO and Agriculture Workshop - Background Material and Planning, 2002 October 18-27 (Box 59, Folder 942)
    Global Implications for Chinese Agriculture in the Post-WTO Environment. Budget and expense materials added to this file.
  - WTO and Agriculture Workshop - Brochure, Itinerary, and Report, 2002 October 18-27 (Box 59, Folder 943)
    Global Implications for Chinese Agriculture in the Post-WTO Environment. Participant passport photos added to this file.
  - WTO and Agriculture Workshop - Participants, 2002 October 18-27 (Box 59, Folder 944)
    Global Implications for Chinese Agriculture in the Post-WTO Environment.
  - WTO and Agriculture Workshop - Possible Participants, 2002 October 18-27 (Box 59, Folder 945)
  - Municipal Finance Workshop - Background and Planning, 2002 November 30-December 11 (Box 59, Folder 946)
    Municipal Finance Workshop: An Environmental Infrastructure Focus.
  - Municipal Finance Workshop - Brochure and Bios, 2002 November 30-December 11 (Box 59, Folder 947)
    Municipal Finance Workshop: An Environmental Infrastructure Focus. File includes some photos.
  - Municipal Finance Workshop - Evaluations, 2002 November 30-December 11 (Box 59, Folder 948)
  - Municipal Finance Workshop - Papers, 2002 November 30-December 11 (Box 59, Folder 949)
    Municipal Finance Workshop: An Environmental Infrastructure Focus. Papers in English by U. S. and Chinese participants.
  - Municipal Finance Workshop - Papers (Chinese Translations), 2002 November 30-December 11 (Box 60, Folder 950)
    Municipal Finance Workshop: An Environmental Infrastructure Focus. Includes translations into Chinese of papers by U. S. participants.
  - Worker Retraining Delegation - Background and Planning, 2003 April 11-19 (Box 60, Folder 951)
    Worker Training /Retraining for Economies in Transition.
  - Worker Retraining Delegation - China Visit, 2003 April 11-19 (Box 60, Folder 952)
    Worker Training /Retraining for Economies in Transition. The NCUSCR postponed the PRC leg of the visit, which had been scheduled for April 17-28, owing to concerns over the SARS outbreak.
  - Worker Retraining Delegation - Papers, 2003 April 11-19 (Box 60, Folder 953)
    Worker Training /Retraining for Economies in Transition
  - Worker Retraining Delegation - Participants, 2003 April 11-19 (Box 60, Folder 954)
    Worker Training /Retraining for Economies in Transition. Includes some photos.
  - Worker Retraining Delegation - Proceedings, 2003 April 11-19 (Box 60, Folder 955)
    Worker Training /Retraining for Economies in Transition. Symposium on Human Resource Development, April 15-16, 2003. Two volumes in Chinese and English, containing agenda, proceedings (in Chinese only), and paper presentations. Includes printed photos of the conference.
  - Worker Retraining Delegation - Taiwan Visit, 2003 April 11-19 (Box 60, Folder 956)
  - Cross-Strait Study Team, 2004 January 4-10 (Box 60, Folder 957)
  - Worker Displacement Delegation - Background Material, 2004 May 31-June 9 (Box 60, Folder 958)
    Workshop on Developing Innovative Policies to Address Worker Displacement.
  - Worker Displacement Delegation - Participant Bios and Information, 2004 May 31-June 9 (Box 60, Folder 959)
    Workshop on Developing Innovative Policies to Address Worker Displacement. Includes some photos.
  - Worker Displacement Delegation - Planning, Schedule, and Follow-Up, 2004 May 31-June 9 (Box 60, Folder 960)
  - Worker Displacement Delegation - Planning, Schedule, and Follow-Up, 2004 May 31-June 9; FA772:034; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 960)
    Group photo of participants.
  - Worker Displacement Delegation - Presentations, 2004 May 31-June 9 (Box 60, Folder 961)
  - Leaders of Minority-Serving Institutions - Correspondence With Participants, 2004 June 8-24 (Box 60, Folder 962)
    Special Seminar for Leaders of Minority Serving Institutions (Fulbright-Hays Seminars Abroad Program)
  - Leaders of Minority-Serving Institutions - Participants, 2004 June 8-24 (Box 61, Folder 963)
  - Leaders of Minority-Serving Institutions - Participants (Personal Information), 2004 June 8-24 (Box 61, Folder 964)
  - Leaders of Minority-Serving Institutions - Planning. Budget, and Final Report, 2004 June 8-24 (Box 61, Folder 965)
  - Leaders of Minority-Serving Institutions - Predeparture Orientation, 2004 June 8-24 (Box 61, Folder 966)
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Background and Planning, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 967)
    Includes Predeparture Briefing agenda.
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Background Material, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 968)
    File contains "ASEM Anti - Money Launfering Initiative, Training and Technical Assistance Needs Analysis, China. Report by Consultants, April 2003."
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Budget and Expenses, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 969)
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Itinerary and Agenda, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 970)
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Papers and Presentations, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 971-972)
    Includes materials in English and Chinese.
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Participants, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 973)
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Report and Follow-Up, 2004 July 16-27 (Box 61, Folder 974)
  - Anti - Money Laundering Delegation - Report and Follow-Up, 2004 July 16-27; FA772:035; Still Images (Box 146, Folder 974)
    Group photo of Seminar in Dalian, July 21, 2004; informal snapshots of delegates.
  - Developing Volunteerism - General, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 975)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. File contains budget materials, correspondence, and proposals. (File also includes copies of proposals submitted in 2003 for programs on promoting open markets, HIV-Aids prevention, and fighting counterfeiting.)
  - Developing Volunteerism - General, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 976)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. File concerns planning and possible participants. Includes Marilyn Champlin correspondence, notes, and copy of proposal to the State Department.
  - Developing Volunteerism - General, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 977)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. File includes powerpoints and copies of namelists from the December programs in China. File also includes brochure and schedule for follow-up internship program in the U.S. in February-April, 2006.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Administrative Documents, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 978)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. Materials relate to representatives' travel arrangements and expenses.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Background and Planning, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 979)
    Background correspondence (from 2002-2005), notes, and budgeting for workshop and training program, Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Background and Planning, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 980)
  - Developing Volunteerism - Background and Planning, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 981)
  - Developing Volunteerism - Background Materials, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 982)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Evaluations, 2005 December (Box 62, Folder 983)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. Evaluations in Chinese. This folder includes a set of evaluations, which had been housed in a separate envelope with the label, Beijing Evaluation Form, Meredith bring U.S.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Evaluations, 2005 December (Box 63, Folder 984)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. Evaluations in Chinese.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Evaluations, 2005 December (Box 63, Folder 985)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. This folder includes a program agenda and powerpoint slides.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Proposal to U. S. Department of State, 2005 December (Box 63, Folder 986)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. Proposal submitted in 2003.
  - Developing Volunteerism - Workshop and Planning Documents, 2005 December (Box 63, Folder 987)
    Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. Includes workshop documents (in Chinese) and some budget and accounting records.
  - John Edwards Visit, 2006 October 16-19 (Box 63, Folder 988)
  - Michael Moskow Visit, 2007 March 22-29 (Box 63, Folder 989)
    Moskow was president of the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago. Includes some materials in Chinese.
  - Municipal Leaders Delegation, 2007 June 15-25 (Box 63, Folder 990)
    National League of Cities / League of California Cities Leadership Delegation.
  - U.S. - China Working Group Staff Delegation, 2007 June 30-July 8 (Box 63, Folder 991)
  - Mayors Delegation on Urban Sustainability and Green Cities, 2008 September (Box 63, Folder 992)
- Exchanges from China, 4
  - Science Education Delegation - Background and Planning, 1982 May 15-June 4 (Box 64, Folder 993)
  - Science Education Delegation - Namelists, Guidelines, and Itineraries, 1982 May 15-June 4 (Box 64, Folder 994)
  - Science Education Delegation - Report, Follow-Up, and Thank Yous, 1982 May 15-June 4 (Box 64, Folder 995)
    Includes paper on "Science Education in the People's Republic of China," by Paul DeHart Hurd, October 1981.
  - African Specialists Delegation - Background and Planning, 1983 May 2-19 (Box 64, Folder 996)
    African specialists from the Institute of West Asian and African Studies of the Chinese Academy of Sciences.
  - African Specialists Delegation - Report, Follow up, and Thank Yous, 1983 May 2-19 (Box 64, Folder 997)
  - Xinjiang Science and Technology Delegation, 1984 October (Box 64, Folder 998)
    Delegation from Xinjiang Uygur Autonomous Region visited from October 6-28, 1984.
  - Local Education Administration Delegation, 1985 March 16-April 4 (Box 64, Folder 999)
  - Film Week Delegation - General, 1985 April 10-29 (Box 64, Folder 1000)
    Includes itinerary and background and planning.
  - Film Week Delegation - Correspondence, 1985 April 10-29 (Box 64, Folder 1001)
  - Film Week Delegation - Report, Follow-Up, and Thank Yous, 1985 April 10-29 (Box 64, Folder 1002)
  - State Economic Commission Delegation - General, 1985 April 20-May 11 (Box 64, Folder 1003)
    Delegation headed by Lu Dong, chair of the State Economic Commission. Includes brochure, itinerary, and background material.
  - State Economic Commission Delegation - Correspondence With China, 1985 April 20-May 11 (Box 64, Folder 1004)
  - State Economic Commission Delegation - Meeting Planning, 1985 April 20-May 11 (Box 64, Folder 1005)
    Correspondence, grouped by city, arranging meetings and other events with the delegation.
  - State Economic Commission Delegation - Report, Follow-Up, and Thank Yous, 1985 April 20-May 11 (Box 64, Folder 1006)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Background and Planning, 1985 April 24-May 12 (Box 64, Folder 1007)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Meetings and Local Itineraries, 1985 April 24-May 12 (Box 64, Folder 1008)
    Correspondence arranged by state.
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Report, Itinerary, and Namelist, 1985 April 24-May 12 (Box 64, Folder 1009)
  - Provincial Governors Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1985 April 24-May 12 (Box 65, Folder 1010)
  - Radio Beijing Delegation - Background and Planning, 1985 April 27-May 12 (Box 65, Folder 1011)
    Visit arranged at request of Voice of America. File includes brochure, guidelines, and itinerary.
  - Radio Beijing Delegation - Meetings and Local Itineraries, 1985 April 27-May 12 (Box 65, Folder 1012)
    Correspondence grouped by city or state.
  - Radio Beijing Delegation - Reports, Final Itinerary, and Thank Yous, 1985 April 27-May 12 (Box 65, Folder 1013)
    Includes material from file labeled "Reports and Final Itinerary for USIA."
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences Delegation, 1985 June 6-13 (Box 65, Folder 1014)
    Visit arranged in conjunction with a conference at the Brookings Institution.
  - Journalists Delegation - General, 1985 June 22-July 12 (Box 65, Folder 1015)
    Also referred to as Media Delegation or Editors Delegation. Includes brochure, guidelines, final itinerary, report, and thank yous.
  - Journalists Delegation - Meetings and Local Itineraries, 1985 June 22-July 12 (Box 65, Folder 1016)
  - Women's Delegation - Background and Planning, 1985 August 28-September 12 (Box 65, Folder 1017)
    Delegation of Young Women Leaders. Includes guidelines.
  - Women's Delegation - Meetings and Local Itineraries, 1985 August 28-September 12 (Box 65, Folder 1018)
  - Women's Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1985 August 28-September 12 (Box 65, Folder 1019)
  - Provincial Colleges and Universities Delegation - Background and Planning, 1985 October 19-November 10 (Box 65, Folder 1020)
  - Provincial Colleges and Universities Delegation - Guidelines, Itineraries, and Meetings, 1985 October 19-November 10 (Box 65, Folder 1021)
  - Provincial Colleges and Universities Delegation - Report, Namelist, Itinerary, and Follow-Up, 1985 October 19-November 10 (Box 65, Folder 1022)
    Report prepared for the USIA.
  - Institute of Contemporary International Relations (ICIR) Delegation - Background and Planning, 1985 November 30 -December 19 (Box 65, Folder 1023)
  - Institute of Contemporary International Relations (ICIR) Delegation - Namelists, Guidelines, Itinerary, and Follow-Up, 1985 November 30 -December 19 (Box 65, Folder 1024)
  - Campus Design and Management Study Team - Background and Planning, 1986 January 4-19 (Box 65, Folder 1025)
  - Campus Design and Management Study Team - Namelist, Guidelines, Itineraries, and Visits, 1986 January 4-19 (Box 65, Folder 1026)
  - Campus Design and Management Study Team - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1986 January 4-19 (Box 65, Folder 1027)